[Music]
[音乐]
本教程讲的很不寻常
this tutorial is about quite an unusual
拉条，拉舌片的地方
出现并翻转所有按键
this tutorial is about quite an unusual
pull strip where you pull the tab a flap
在下面是一个小条
有5个部分，其中的关键
pull strip where you pull the tab a flap
appears and flips over the key to it all
机制，所以我已经掌握了一切
准备在这里，这是它的基础
appears and flips over the key to it all
is a little strip underneath here which
这里有一个折痕，所以当你看这个
一个底端折叠，所以
is a little strip underneath here which
has 5 sections there the key to the
那里的折痕我也放了一条折痕
向下两侧，所以您有标签
has 5 sections there the key to the
mechanism so I've got all the pieces
那里的标签会折叠
它关闭了，所以我就把它们剪下来
mechanism so I've got all the pieces
prepared here this is the base it's got
您可以看到它是如何实际制成的
截面是10厘米，这是15
prepared here this is the base it's got
a crease here so when you look at this
厘米
我把这些剪掉
a crease here so when you look at this
one the bottom end folds over so that's
这是您的基础表，这是
像这样折叠起来的
one the bottom end folds over so that's
the crease there I've also put a crease
拍打五厘米乘五厘米
厘米，这是小条
the crease there I've also put a crease
down each side so you've got tabs so
一切的关键
我会给它打分，这样一切都会动起来
down each side so you've got tabs so
that there's tabs here which will fold
真的很顺利
所以就在这里，我们只是折痕全部
that there's tabs here which will fold
it shut so I'll just cut those off so
那些真的很好，所以他们真的移动
组装好后，
it shut so I'll just cut those off so
you can see how it's actually made this
地带，最后的地带将
粘在第二条上
you can see how it's actually made this
section is 10 centimeters and this is 15
会粘在平坦的地方
会像那样
section is 10 centimeters and this is 15
centimeters
所以我就把那一块粘在一个
从末尾开始
centimeters
I'll just cut these off
像那样
然后带着所有这些东西
this is your base sheet and this is
拉带是双重疾病，所以我已经
已经打分了
this is your base sheet and this is
going to fold over like this here's the
我已经把它折好了
特别强壮，我们会背靠背粘上
going to fold over like this here's the
flap five centimeters by five
我们将它们折叠起来，然后将它们粘在
尽头，但我们只是折入
flap five centimeters by five
centimeters this is the little strip the
事先，这将胶合
拉带去这里，这是
centimeters this is the little strip the
key to it all that flips it over
要粘在拉带上
这将粘在这里，所以我只是
key to it all that flips it over
I'll just score it so it'll all move
检查距离并拉动
这样出来，这将是
I'll just score it so it'll all move
really smoothly
像这样，这将是失败的
当它粘在适当的地方时
so here it is and we just crease all
像这样，但有襟翼
在下面，这将是
so here it is and we just crease all
those really well so they move really
在下面，我们现在在上面涂胶
底端
those really well so they move really
nicely when it's all assembled take the
所以就像胶水一样
放置在翻转时可以翻转
nicely when it's all assembled take the
strip and the very end strip is going to
这样，只要确定何时
就像这样
strip and the very end strip is going to
stick onto the full strip the second bit
要坚持在那里
只要确保它在拉动时有效
stick onto the full strip the second bit
is going to stick onto the flat it's
出现并稍微翻转我的
坚持下去，一切正常
is going to stick onto the flat it's
going to be like that
我的测量略有偏差，所以我
一分钟内将其修剪掉，但是
going to be like that
so I'll just glue that piece on one
首先，我要坚持这两个目的
下来，另一件事是你需要一个
so I'll just glue that piece on one
section in from the end so that's going
像这样滑脱
将经历，以便它可以是
section in from the end so that's going
to be like that
保持原位并移动得很好，所以我会
只是标记要去的地方
and then with all these things they'll
在我将其折叠之前就在这里
我就把它切开
and then with all these things they'll
pull strip is double sickness so I've
通过并粘这些位
你看我有点乱
pull strip is double sickness so I've
already scored it
我到处都有胶水
稍微关闭，所以我会剪一点
already scored it
I've already folded it now to make it
一点点蓝色消失了
我们去了那里，你得到了这个翻转
I've already folded it now to make it
extra strong we'll glue it back to back
在最后一件事上，你实际上可以
修剪这尾巴下来，所以推
we'll just fold these so we glue them at
它会像这样延伸
推入它就可以修剪它
we'll just fold these so we glue them at
the very ends but we'll just fold in
离开，所以你只有一点点
所以你可以用它来
the very ends but we'll just fold in
beforehand and this is going to glue in
在这里有一个惊喜消息或
你可以说快乐的惊喜形象
beforehand and this is going to glue in
the pull strips going to go here this is
生日，你可以嫁给我吗
一条消息，然后是下一则
the pull strips going to go here this is
going to glue onto the pull strip and
在那里你也可以写一篇
里面有各种各样的东西
going to glue onto the pull strip and
this is going to glue in here so I just
出现然后突然更多
看来你也可能有某种
this is going to glue in here so I just
check the distance in and it's pulled
图片在这里，当您将其拉出时
而那可以改变
check the distance in and it's pulled
out like this this end this is going to
可以作为基本图像的补充
你必须从头开始
out like this this end this is going to
be like this this is going to be down
这一点扩展了你，你可能
玩这个，所以你有
be like this this is going to be down
here when it's glued in place it's going
拉出并翻动皮瓣惊喜
[音乐]
here when it's glued in place it's going
to be like this but with the flap
[掌声]
[音乐]
to be like this but with the flap
underneath so that's going to be